{
    "subject": "resource/Silapathar",
    "predicate": "property/lats",
    "object": "43",
    "human_readable": "Silapathar is located at latitude 43.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8635920882225037,
            "question": "What is the latitude of Silapathar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8295609354972839,
            "question": "Where is Silapathar located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8071439266204834,
            "question": "Can you provide a geographical description of Silapathar based on its latitude?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7998648285865784,
            "question": "At what coordinates can you find Silapathar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7116718888282776,
            "question": "If someone wanted to visit Silapathar, what latitude should they set their GPS to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6680929064750671,
            "question": "What can be inferred about the climate of Silapathar based on its latitude?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6395097374916077,
            "question": "How would you describe the location of Silapathar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6235621571540833,
            "question": "Is Silapathar situated in a northern or southern hemisphere?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6179189682006836,
            "question": "Is there any other information needed to accurately describe the location of Silapathar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6174465417861938,
            "question": "What geographical information is provided about Silapathar?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Silapathar is located at latitude 43.",
            "html": "dbpedia_687_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any other information needed to accurately describe the location of Silapathar?",
            "html": "dbpedia_687_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Silapathar situated in a northern or southern hemisphere?",
            "html": "dbpedia_687_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the location of Silapathar?",
            "html": "dbpedia_687_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_687_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_687_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_687_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_687_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_687_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_687_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_687_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_687_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_687_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_687_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because none of the documents mention that Silapathar is located at latitude 43. The correct latitude for Silapathar is mentioned as 27.59441 and longitude of 94.72402 in document 26.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the location of Silapathar, including its geographic coordinates. According to the document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_687/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt` and others, the latitude is 26.2059700, not 43."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}